(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-01T22:46:13.667456",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Good day, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to the Queen Mother Theater.
May I remind you to unwrap the snacks you may wish to nom,
and please switch your mobile phones ON, as photography IS allowed!
Please feel free to take screenshots during the performance using the hashtag...
...#ERB3D.
Spread your Queen's performance far and wide.
本日は、クイーンマザーシアターへご来場いただき、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for coming to the Queen Mother Theater today.
開演に先立ち、いくつかご案内申し上げます。
Prior to the start of the show, we have a few announcements.
館内での飲食は大歓迎です。
Eating and drinking inside the venue is very welcome.
お手元のお菓子は、どうぞご自由にお楽しみください。
Please feel free to enjoy the snacks you have on hand.
本公演は撮影OK。
Taking photos during this performance is allowed.
携帯電話は電源ONのままで、
Please leave your mobile phones switched on,
スクリーンショットには「#ERB3D」のハッシュタグを添え、
and add the hashtag #ERB3D to your screenshots.
ぜひSNSでご投稿して、女王陛下の魅力を世界の隅々までお届けください。
Please post them on social media and spread Her Majesty's charm to every corner of the world.
Thank you!
And enjoy the performance!
Huzzah!
さあ、それでは間もなく開演のお時間です。
Now then, it will soon be time for the show to begin.
どうぞお席にて、女王陛下の舞台を心ゆくまでお楽しみください。
Please enjoy Her Majesty the Queen's stage performance to your heart's content from your seats.
ハッツァー！
Huzzah!
Attah!
Hey, hey, get off me!
What the freak?
Get out of my way!
I don't have time to deal with the likes of you!
Get back... and take this!
Phew! Blimey.
Know your place!
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
And those who dare interfere with me shall receive no mercy!
Good grief.
And today of all days, my commemorative 3D showcase!
Getting ambushed like this has been... quite troublesome.
Sod's law! With all the showcase preparations and practice I need to do...
I can't afford to waste time on something like this.
There's not enough hours in the day.
How annoying!
All right, you pop yourself there, Thorns. Stay there, stay there.
Listen to this: my self-introduction!
I shall practice.
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue!
Also known as the Scarlet Queen, the Harbinger of Order,
Leader of Justice!
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Lovely to see you, to see you! Lovely!
All right, well, how was that?
Tough crowd.
Oh gosh! I'm so behind!
We need to get to the karaoke stage!
Come on, Thorns! Let's go!
What the freak?
You lot again?
You never learn, do you?
All right, I guess it's time for round two!
Get off!
Ow! Oh my god, ow!
You dare wound my flames?
You'll pay for this!
Very well.
I'll deal with you...
...while practicing a song for my 3D showcase!
Two birds, one stone!
Listen well.
Huzza!
半端なら K.O.
Half-ass deserves a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
So be it, if you're light-hearted
開演準備しちゃおうか
Let's get ready for the show
泣いても笑っても愛してね
Cry or laugh, just love me okay?
ほら say no
Come on, say no
低音響かせろ
Now let's bring the bass
なんだかな…ってつまんないこともあるでしょう
Don't know what to say, things tend to get boring
ロンリー論理のノート ハンディー本気脱走
Lonely logic note, handy serious escape
やんなっちゃって泥に bad
Can't take this anymore, it's bad
ご法度だろうが溺れて堕ちて
Though taboo, I'll drown and fall
そろそろいっか
It's about time
もっと頑張って
Let's work harder
アガるまでもっと頑張って
Let me work harder until I get excited
繋がろうひとりよりふたり
Let's connect, two is better than one
増えたら安心 心配ないや
More people means relief, no worries at all
Alright 任せて don't mind
Alright, leave it to me, don't mind
波あり難題
Riding waves of trouble
みんなで乗っかっちゃえば
If we all jump on together
案外さくっと行っちゃいそう
It might actually go smoothly
半端なら K.O.
Half-ass deserves a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
So be it, if you're light-hearted
開演準備しちゃおうか
Let's get ready for the show
泣いても笑っても愛してね
Cry or laugh, just love me okay
ほら say no
Come on, say no
低音響かせろ
Now let's bring the bass
今宵は暗転パーティー
Tonight's a party in the dark
踊りだせ 踊りだせ
Dance, dance
孤独は殺菌 満員御礼
Sanitize loneliness, it's a full house, thank you
痛みまで おシェアで
Let's share even the pain
ここらでバイバイ let go
It's time to say bye-bye, let go
どんな劣等感だって
Any kind of inferiority complex
即興の血小板で
With an improvised platelet
抑え込んで 突っ込んで
Hold it down, charge right in
仕舞っちゃうでしょう
And put it all away
Up and down なテンション
Pumped up and down tension
ねえまいっちゃってんの相当
Hey, I'm pretty overwhelmed
ドバッと噴き出すのは
What gushes right out
本音の独り言
Is a monologue of true feelings
「別に興味ない」
"Not really interested"
「特に関係ない」
"Doesn't really concern me"
塞ぎ込んで
Closing yourself off
舌鋒頂点へ
To the peak of sharp tongue
半端なら K.O. ほら勝つまで Ya
If you're half-assed, it's K.O., until I win, ya...
夜が明けるまで A-A-y, Yeah
Until daybreak, a-a-y, yeah.
泣いていこう
Let me keep crying through.
パラパッパッ...
Pa-ra-pa-pa...
重なる K.O.
Overlapping K.O.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Woo-ow-ow, woo-ow-ow
踊り出せ 踊り出せ 言葉はいらない 黙りの例え
Start dancing, start dancing! No words needed, silence says it all.
Woo-ow-ow, woo-ow-ow
言い足りない 飽き足りない 宵の舞 テンパっていこうぜ
Can't say enough, can't get enough, evening dance, let's lose control!
Yeah, woo-ow-ow
場の空気を乱してゆこう
Let's stir up the mood of the place!
Woo-ow-ow, woo-ow-ow
限界までお元気で くだらねぇバイバイ Let's go
Take care till your limit, foolish bye-bye, let's go!
This is the end!
Huzzah!
Is that the last of them?
My flame... It grows small due to my nerves.
I need to shake it off. I can't appear before everyone like this.
My phone...
What the freak?!
My karaoke room booking plus! I don't have a lot of time till the showcase!
Huzzah!
Okay! All right, time to get to karaoke. Come on, Thorn.
Onwards and upwards!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, sorry, sorry, sorry!
ごめん! All right...
Sorry! All right...
Goodbye! Parting is such sweet sorrow, but I will see you on the morrow!
Thank you, thank you!
Until the next battle, yes, all right! Off we go! Huzzah!
All right.
Let me go!
Heaven, please sing for me a song of life
Heaven, take me into your skies
There's no place here for me to hide my cries
Night and day, I'm missing you
I know I'm here for the magic
All your stars guiding me through and through
Oh, why this loneliness feel like... forever and ever
I gotta be, I gotta be in your arms, baby
You're so close, so close, and it's you that I believe in, I believe in
So close, but faraway, so far I can't touch
I'll hold on, 'cause it's you I love so dearly
When the rain, the storm, and all is done
Caress me with your sweet lullaby
Heaven, please sing for me a song of life
Heaven, save me in my dreams tonight
Someday these wings will perish in your sight
Night and day, I call for you
Flashes of moments so tragic
Wandering souls, they fall along the way
Tell me you will never leave me forever and ever
I gotta be, I gotta be in your arms, hear me
So close, so close, and it's you that I believe in, I believe in
So close, but far away, I seek for your light
I'll hold on 'cause for you my heart keeps beating
When the wind, the fire, and all is gone
Caress me with your sweet lullaby...
Will you be my light?
Will you be my strength?
Promise you won't let me go...
I'll never betray in the end of time
Still my love's gonna be there...
So close, so close, and it's you that I believe in, I believe in
So close, but far away, so far I can't touch
I'll hold on 'cause it's you I love so dearly
When the rain, the storm, and all is done
Caress me with your sweet lullaby...
So close, so close, and it's you that I believe in, I believe in
So close, but far away, I seek for your light
I'll hold on 'cause for you my heart keeps beating
When the wind, the fire, and all is gone
Caress me with your sweet lullaby...
This song is lovely, but for my showcase performance, should I pick nostalgic songs?
Oh, it's a call!
Rys! My favorite kouhai! How are you, BB?
Ollie-senpai! Perfect timing. Actually, I'm having trouble deciding what to sing for my 3D showcase...
Is that so? Though I think I speak for everyone when I say we'll be happy to hear you sing anything! As long as you're enjoying yourself, that is!
But isn't it standard to pick songs that match your image? There's like an expectation to be cool, right? But since this is a special occasion and all, I was thinking maybe I should show other sides of myself...
I see! Well, you know how powerful you look when you sing? Well, I thought, you know, why not try a cute song instead? Go for that gap moe appeal, you know what I'm sayin'?
A cute song? That would be different from usual, which would be good, but I'm a bit worried about doing it alone...
Ah! That's it! What if we invited my brothers in arm, ARMIS, as guests?
That's a great idea! Seeing cool people singing cute songs... oh, the gap moe will definitely get everybody excited!
U-Uh, but it's still a tad embarrassing...
It'll be fine! Come on, try imagining it! Picture you and ARMIS singing a cute song together!
Okay... Me and ARMIS... cute song... t-t-together?!
私が私の事を愛して
I love myself,
何が悪い no? 嫉妬でしょうか？
what's wrong with that? Are you just jealous?
痛いだとか変ってるとか
Saying I'm cringey or odd,
届きませんね そのリプライ
those replies don't reach me.
大好きなお洋服
Wearing my favorite clothes
大好きなお化粧で
and my favorite makeup,
お決まりのハー フツイン巻いて
curling my usual half-twintails,
お出かけしよう
let me go out!
日傘持って
With my parasol,
ぼっちだって
even if I'm all alone,
幸せだもん
I'm still happy!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute!
生まれてきちゃってごめん
Sorry that I was born!
Chu! あざとくてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so calculatingly cute!
気になっちゃうよね？ごめん
You can't help but notice me, right? Sorry!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute!
努力しちゃっててごめん
Sorry for working so hard on myself!
Chu! 尊くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so precious!
女子力高くてごめん
Sorry for having such high girl power!
ムカついちゃうよね？ざまあw
It pisses you off, right? Serves you right!
貴女は貴女の事だけどうぞ 私に干渉施しないでください
You go worry about yourself, please don't interfere with me.
類は友を呼ぶと言うけど… 届きませんね その陰口
They say birds of a feather flock together... but your gossip doesn't reach me.
重い厚底ブーツ
Wearing heavy platform boots
お気に入りのリュックで
and my favorite backpack,
崩せない前髪 くしでといで
combing my flawless bangs with a comb,
お出かけしよう
let me go out!
軽い女？ふざけんな
An easy girl? Don't mess with me!
重すぎるっつーの！
I'm way too heavy!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute!
この時代生きてごめん
Sorry for living in this era!
Chu! 目立っててごめん
Chu! Sorry for standing out!
意識しちゃうよね？ごめん
You can't help but notice me, right? Sorry!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute!
自分磨きしてごめん
Sorry for working on myself!
Chu! ぶりっ子でごめん
Chu! Sorry for acting cute!
虜にしちゃってごめん
Sorry for making you fall for me!
ムカついちゃうでしょ？ざまあw
It pisses you off, right? Serves you right!
趣味の違い 変わり者と
Having different tastes, being called weird,
バカにされても 負けてない 怖くもない
even if I'm made fun of, I won't lose and I'm not scared!
あんたらごとき
People like you...
自分の味方は自分でありたい
I want to be my own ally.
一番大切にしてあげたい
I want to cherish myself the most.
理不尽な我慢はさせたくない
I don't want to endure unreasonable things.
“それが私”
"That's who I am!"
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute!
生まれてきちゃってごめん
Sorry that I was born!
Chu! あざとくてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so calculatingly cute!
人生楽しんでごめん
Sorry for enjoying my life!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute!
努力しちゃっててごめん
Sorry for working so hard on myself!
Chu! 尊くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so precious!
女子力高くてごめん
Sorry for having such high girl power!
ムカついちゃうよね？ざまあw
It pisses you off, right? Serves you right!
Gah, no! You know, maybe... maybe I'm not cut out to be a cu-cu-cu-cute girl like that!
That's not true! I'm sure everyone wants to see that side of you too, Liz!
So thank you, yeah! I feel better about it since you think so, Ollie-senpai! Makes me happy you think I'm cu... I'm powerful!
Powerful indeed!
Oh, gosh! Seems like it's the end of my karaoke room booking rehearsal time is up here! Ollie-senpai, thank you so, so much!
Do your best, Liz!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
I shall! Okay, here we go.
Okay, let me go, let me go! Oh, come on!
All right, here we go! Woo!
Hmm, my singing is fine...
...but now the physical performance side of bits and bobs is what worries me.
I'm really not too confident...
...about my dancing as I'm... a tad rusty.
Oh! What's wrong, Liz?
Shiori-senpai! Wow...
Well, actually, I've been worried about my showcase performance...
...as it's getting closer and closer, and I'm not very confident about my dancing.
Is that all? Don't worry! Don't worry!
When it comes to dancing, as long as you convey your passion...
...mistakes don't even exist!
Ah, yeah, true. But I'm still a bit worried.
Well, in that case, how about this?
Come to my Jazz club!
If we practice together, I'm sure you'll have more of a spring in your step!
Wait, right now? Well, that's really nice of you, Shiori-senpai, but...
Okay, follow me, Liz!
Oh, yeah... I'm dancing.
Let's move and groove!
Wait, Shiori-senpai! Wait, what do you mean by move and groove? Woah, what the hey?!
ギリギリで愛し合いましょう
Let's love each other to the limit
嘘もモエツクシテ 夢にして
Burn away those lies and make it a dream
冗談じゃない もっと踊りたい
I'm not joking, I want to dance more
もう我慢できない
I can't hold back anymore
愛を 愛を 愛を 打ち明けてくれ
Express your love, love, love to me
あぶないね その笑顔
Your smile is dangerous
心乱されて 欲しくなる
It messes with my heart and makes me want you
優等生なんて嘘でしょう
Being a good student must be a lie
はぐらかしてじれったい
Dodging the question, it's so frustrating
どうにかなりそう
I feel like I'm going crazy
くちづけるほどに足らなくなる
The more we kiss, the less it feels like enough
抱き寄せたら意外なほど
When I pull you close, surprisingly
寂しい目で睨むから
You glare with such lonely eyes
ゲ・ン・カイ・ダ・ダ・ダ・ダ
I'm at my li-li-limit!
ギラギラな夢を見せてよ
Show me a dazzling dream
ぜんぶばらまいて 星にして
Scatter everything and turn it into stars
純情じゃない ところも知りたい
I want to know the un-pure side of you too
もう我慢できない
I can't hold back anymore
愛を 愛を 愛を 打ち明けてくれ
Express your love, love, love to me
Your turn! My turn? Okay!
ドラマなんて飽きたでしょう
You must be tired of drama, right?
ふたりだけの最終回描かなくちゃ
We have to draw our own final episode
運命だななんてじゃれ合って
Playfully talking about destiny
演じきればいいじゃない
Why not just play the part to the end?
不躾な言葉で また覚悟を試してくるのに
Even as you test my resolve with impudent words again
「ひとりきりにさせないでよ」と哀しい目で笑うから
You smile with sad eyes saying, "Don't leave me all alone"
ズ・ル・イ・ヨ・ナ・ナ・ナ・ナ
You're so unfair!
ギリギリな恋人たちは
Lovers on the edge
切ないこの夜も満たせるね
Can fulfill even this painful night
理性じゃない もっと奥の方
Not with reason, but from deep down within
ふるえてヤバくなる
Trembling, it gets dangerous
愛を 愛を 愛を曝け出してくれ
Expose your love, love, love to me
泣かないでそれ以上 心撃ち抜かないで
Don't cry anymore, don't pierce my heart like that
潤ませた瞳にもう狂わされてしまう
I'm already driven mad by your teary eyes
完璧な敗北さ もう離せなんかしない
It's a complete defeat, I won't ever let go
この指を この愛を
This finger, this love
完璧な敗北さ
It's a complete defeat
もう離せなんかしない
I won't ever let go
この指を この指を
This finger, this finger
この愛を
This love
ギリギリで信じて欲しい
I want you to believe in me to the limit
ふたりなら真実になれる
Together, we can make it real
告白は最後の誓いさ もう抱きしめたいよ
A confession is our final oath, I want to hold you now
ギリギリで愛し合いましょう
Let's love each other to the limit
嘘も燃え尽くして夢にして
Burn away those lies and make it a dream
冗談じゃない
I'm not joking
もっと踊りたい
I want to dance more
もう我慢できない
I can't hold it anymore
愛を 愛を 愛を 打ち明けてくれ
Let me confess this love away
So, how was it? Once you get into it, it's a good feeling, right?
Dance like nobody's watching, have fun!
Yes! Somehow, I really gained confidence. Thank you, Raora-senpai!
Oh, Liz. You always tell others mistakes help them grow and believing in themselves.
You really need to start taking your own advice.
Listen to your own heart's flame, let that be your strength.
Yeah, you're right. Sometimes...
...I forget, but thank you for reminding me.
Guess I'm only human.
Here, let me help you take that off.
Hey, but I look so dapper though, in it!
Looks cool.
Ouch...
With you, Liz, I'm sure your debut will be wonderful.
I'm looking forward to it!
As you say, believe in me!
Who believes in thee!
Huzzah!
Well, the preparations for the showcase seem to be going smoothly.
So much has happened since we infiltrated Holo. Songs, performances...
...troubles, challenges, and kind words too.
All of them are irreplaceable memories I'll cherish forever.
I want to do my best for my family, my friends, my kingdom...
...and of course, my talented girlies... Justice.
Onwards and upwards!
Flame off.
Phew, still, it's been such a busy day.
Maybe I should rest for a bit.
Yeah, a little nap won't hurt anybody.
Manager says I should nap anyways, so it's fine...
一番の宝物 ~Yui final ver.~
[Title: My Most Precious Treasure ~Yui final ver.~]
顔をあわせたら
Whenever we saw each other,
喧嘩してばかり
all we did was fight.
それもいい思い出だった
But those were also good memories.
君が教えてくれたんだ
You were the one who taught me,
もう怖くない
I'm not scared anymore.
どんな不自由でも
No matter how restricted I am,
幸せは掴める だから
I can still grab hold of happiness, so...
ひとりでもゆくよ
I'll go on my own,
たとえつらくても
even if it's painful.
君と見た夢は 必ず持ってくよ
The dream I saw with you, I'll definitely carry it with me.
君とがよかった
I'm glad it was with you...
...った ほかの誰でもない
...was you, and no one else.
でも目覚めた朝 きみは居ないんだね
But when I woke up this morning, you weren't there...
ずっと遊んでれる そんな気がしてた
I felt like we could play together forever...
気がしていただけ わかってる
...I know that was just a feeling.
生まれてきたこと もう後悔はしない
I no longer regret being born into this world.
祭りの後みたい 寂しいけどそろそろ行こう
Like after a festival, it's lonely, but it's time to go.
どこまでもゆくよ ここで知ったこと
I'll go anywhere, holding what I learned here,
幸せという夢を 叶えてみせるよ
and I'll show you I can make the dream of happiness come true.
きみと離れても どんなに遠くなっても
Even if I'm separated from you, no matter how far away we get,
新しい朝に あたしは生きるよ
I will go on living into the new morning.
ひとりでもゆくよ 死にたくなっても
I'll go even on my own, even if I want to give up and die,
声が聞こえるよ 死んではいけないと
I can hear your voice telling me not to die.
例え辛くても 寂しさに泣いても
Even if it's painful, even if I cry in loneliness,
心の奥には 温もりを感じるよ
deep inside my heart, I can feel your warmth.
巡って流れて 時は移ろいだ
Ebbing and flowing, time has shifted.
もう何があったか 思い出せないけど
I can no longer remember what happened back then,
目を閉じてみれば 誰かの笑い声
but if I close my eyes, I can hear someone's laughter.
なぜかそれが今 一番の宝物
For some reason, that is now my most precious treasure.
ひとりでもゆくよ
I will go, even on my own...
どこまでもゆくよ
I'll go anywhere...
Mm... Oh, that dream.
What a beautiful, touching song.
You know what? I should probably add that to my showcase.
My showcase?!
Oh no! Flame on!
Oh gosh, I'm going to be late for my showcase! What the fudge?!
All right, my showcase, my showcase, my showcase!
Open, ye door! Let's go! Come on!
Rosarians!
My Bloodflame Kingdom!
How is the performance thus far?
Let me know what you all think using the hashtag...
#ERB3D! ERB 3D!
What have you loved most thus far?
Is it this beautiful theater, the Queen Mother Theater...
...named after my mum? Hi, Mum! Hello!
Was it Ollie's appearance, Flayon and Oga's voiceovers...
...Kawaikute Gomen sung with ARMIS, Giri Giri with ZEA?
Oh gosh, it'll make me stupidly-doopah happy...
...hearing your thoughts!
And by the way, I can see you all right now! Oh my gosh, I see you guys!
I've seen you at the corner of my eye with a magical, invisible...
...box made by the Rosarian invisible wizards!
So I can see you all right now! Oh my gosh!
This is crazy! What do you think about my 3D appearance, huh?
Let me know in chat right now what poses you would like to see!
Yeah, yeah, let me know! Yeah, let me know!
While you're doing that, I'm going to go get Thorn!
Yeah! It's the one, the only...
...Thorn!
Hello, I'm Thorn!
Let's do a quick pose with Thorn, shall we?
Hazzah! Hazzah!
All right, let's see what you guys have put.
A cat pose?
All right, sure! Let me just put Thorn over here.
Let's take the jacket off for this one. Flame off!
Okay. I need to become... rawr-ra!
Nya! Nya, nya!
Nya! Nya, nya! Nya! Nya!
T-pose?
Okay! That one's easy!
Yes! I shall assert my dominance on you all!
Oh, you know what I want to do?
I want to headpat you all!
Come here! Headpat! Headpat, headpat, headpat!
And hug! Hug! We must do this, we must... hug!
Hug, hug! One more!
We got to, we got to!
What else have you got?
Victory pose?
Like this?
Ha!
Yes! I am victorious! For I am...
...the queen of the Bloodflame kingdom!
Yeah!
I love you all very much too.
I'm so happy you're all here.
Oh gosh.
Absolute cinema, yes.
Okay.
Oh, a twirl?
Okay, we shall do a twirl.
All right.
Yes.
A twirl.
Woah!
Is that okay?
A twirl.
Jazz hands.
Spin!
Spinna!
Doina!
Oh gosh. A curtsy. Oh, that's a good one.
Like this?
A curtsy.
And a bow.
Cute? Hey, you mean... you mean...
...you mean powerful, right?
Powerful.
Powerful!
Yes, yes, yes, powerful.
Rawr!
I know you guys also like my shocked face.
So let me just think of something real, that's shocking.
The frick?!
What the frick?!
What the frick? Time is nearly up for poses?!
Oh, I guess it's time...
...for the next song!
Would you like to hear another song?
Yes! Sure you do!
All right, just wait one moment. I need some...
...some bits and bobs for this one.
All right.
Some bits and the bobs, and the bobs and the bits.
Here we go. Here's the bits...
...and the bobs.
I have a stand.
It's my mic! Look at that!
And I have a guitar.
Ha! I'm so かっこいい!
Ha! I'm so cool!
All right.
Let's go with a... with a cute...
...I mean a powerful song next!
Please listen to...
わたしの恋はホッチキス
My Love is a Stapler.
The next song is My Love is a Stapler.
Let's go!
なんてなんだろう
Why is it, somehow,
気になる夜 キミへの
on this restless night,
この思い便せんにね
these feelings towards you,
書いてみるよ
I try writing them on stationery.
もしかして
Could it be
気まぐれかもしれない
that it's just a whim?
それなのに枚数だけ
Even so, only the page count
増えてゆくよ
keeps on increasing.
好きの確率
If only there were a formula
わりだす計算式
to calculate the chances of love,
あればいいのに
that would be nice,
いいのに
so nice...
キラキラひかる願い事も
Both sparkling, shining wishes
グチャグチャへたる悩み事も
and messy, depressing worries,
そーだ ホッチキスで
that's it! With a stapler,
とじちゃおう
let's staple them together!
はじまりだけは軽いノリで
It started off just light-heartedly,
しらないうちにあつくなって
but grew passionate before I knew it,
もう針がなんだか通らない
and now the staples somehow won't go through.
ララ☆また明日
La la, see you tomorrow.
どうしようかな
What should I do?
読み返すのはずかしい
It's embarrassing to read back,
あれこれと便せんにね
even though I wrote all sorts of things
書いたくせに
on the stationery.
気持ちごと
Throwing these feelings
ゴミ箱行きじゃなんだか
into the trash can feels kinda...
この胸がせつないから
...painful for my heart,
持っていようかな
so maybe I'll hold onto them.
今の気持ちを表す
To express my current feelings,
辞書にもない言葉さがすよ
I'll search for words not even in the dictionary.
...ない
...not even in a dictionary,
言葉探すよ
I'll search for words.
ワクワクしちゃう計画とか
Whether it's an exciting plan,
グダグダすぎる展開とか
or a development that drags on too much,
全部ホッチキスでとじちゃおう
I'll staple them all together with a stapler!
今日の出来事思い出して
Recalling today's events,
いつも心がキュンとなって
my heart always feels a squeeze.
もう針がないから買わなくちゃ
And since I have no more staples left, I gotta go buy some.
ララ☆また明日
La la ☆ See you tomorrow!
キラキラひかる願い事も
Sparkling and shining wishes,
グチャグチャへたる悩み事も
and messy, tiresome worries,
そうだホッチキスでとじちゃおう
that's right, I'll staple them together with a stapler!
始まりだけは軽いノリで
Only the beginning felt light,
知らないうちに熱くなって
while I wasn't aware, it got thick,
もう針がなんだか通らない
and somehow the staple won't go through anymore!
ララ☆また明日
La la ☆ See you tomorrow!
Woo!
And that was "My Love Is a Stapler"!
How was it? Did you like my guitar playing?
I... well, you guys didn't know this,
but I'm actually a professional air guitarist.
I know, I know.
Surprise, shocker! Professional air guitarist here.
Look out!
Anyhoo, now it's time for an announcement!
Everyone, let's call for our favorite four-legged friend, Bobby!
Three, two, one, Bobby!
Come here, Bobby! You're such a good boy. You're a good boy!
Yeah! Show yourself to the camera. Do a little twirl or something, yeah.
Oh, you're so cute! Wait a minute, what the freak?
Bobby! Wait, should we...
Come here, come here, come here.
Up we get.
Eyes, he's such a little cheeky guy, little cheeky guy.
Oh golly!
Well, as you can see on Bobby's head, the announcement is...
Merchandise!
Oh my goodness, we have this!
Ta-da!
Wow! A paper knife, letter opener inspired by my sword Thorn.
A set product that includes an acrylic stand where you can plop your mini Thorn into.
It looks real cool on your desk, and you'll get all the maidens.
I should know, a lot of them have visited my dressing room to see the prototype.
And that's no lie, it's pretty awesome!
And also, the sales dates will be after the Justice collaboration stream.
So once that's all done and dusted, it'll be out there on the shop.
And that concludes the merchandise.
Thank you, Bobby. Everybody thank Bobby.
Thank you, Bobby! Thank you so much. You're such a good boy, you're such a good boy, yes you are, yes you are.
All right, back to the Duke and the Queen Mother you go.
Oh gosh, I honestly can't believe it. Time has flown.
And it's already time for our last, final seventh song, seven!
This has been quite the journey and a half. So before I end, I just want to thank everyone.
The cast, our wonderful guests, the crew, managers, the director,
thank you so much. Thank you for your hard work, thank you, thank you so much.
And of course, my friends, my family, my beautiful kingdom,
thanks for supporting me so much. I wouldn't be standing here right now,
not only do I get to fight for justice, but with my wonderful girlies, Raora, Gigi...
...see... and Cecilia...
But I also get to do what I love.
So thank you so much.
I get to give the gift of smiles...
...and strength for the art of performance and singing.
I hope I can do this forever...
...and we can keep spreading smiles throughout the realms together.
That would make me so happy!
Anyway, before the allergies hit me too much...
...let me just move my stand.
Woah...
The allergies, guys! The allergies!
I can't stand this stand!
It must get out of the way!
Don't mind me!
All right. Uh, wait a minute.
Before I do my last tune...
...we got to bring back my beautiful backing dancers, right?
Come on! Flame on!
And they're back!
Are you ready?
Yes, yes, yes!
And now, for our final song...
...please listen to "Hero too".
Hands up!
I want to be an idol...
...and a hero for all of you too!
Let's go!
Onwards and upwards! Huzzah!
What am I to be?
What is my calling?
I gave up giving up, I'm ready to go
The future's left unseen
It all depends on me
Put it on the line to follow my dream, yeah
Tried all my life
I've tried to find
Something that makes me hold on and never let go
Oh!
Hero too, I am a hero too
My heart is set and I won't back down
Hero too, strength doesn't make a hero
True heroes stand up for what they believe
So wait and see
Yeah!
What do they think of me?
Who do they think I'll be?
I could not care less, I don't wanna know
Am I doing right?
Am I satisfied?
I wanna live my life like it's meant to be, yeah
Tried all my life
I've tried to find
Something that makes me hold on and never let go
Oh!
Hero too, I am a hero too
My heart is set and I won't back down
Hero too, strength doesn't make a hero
True heroes stand up for what they believe
So wait and see
People will judge for no reason at all
Yeah, they might try to say your dream's dumb
Don't listen
They may look down on me
And count me out
I'm going my own way
They may look down on me
And count me out
I'm a hero, I've got music!
Hero too, I am a hero too
My heart is set and I won't back down
Hero too, strength doesn't make a hero
True heroes stand up for what they believe
Yeah, I'll be!
Hero too, I am a hero too
My heart is set and I won't back down
Huzzah!
Hero too, strength doesn't make a hero
True heroes stand up for what they believe
So wait and see
I have met so many heroes in my life
Gave me the strength and courage to survive
Gave me the power to smile every day
Now it's my turn
To be the one to make you smile!
Yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
To make you smile!
Yeah!
Parting is such sweet sorrow, but I will see you on the morrow!
Make sure to eat good nams, mogu mogu!
Make sure to eat good num-nums, munch munch!
Hydrate, mizu mizu!
Hydrate, sip sip!
And get good sleeps, nemu nemu!
And get good sleeps, sleep tight!
As we want our Bloodflame Kingdom to be happy and strong!
大きくなれ！
Grow big and strong!
Let's try our best together!
これからも一緒に頑張ろう！
Let's keep working hard together from now on!
Onwards and upwards!
And don't forget that my voice is your strength!
チュチュチュ！
Mwah, mwah, mwah!
Cheer for everyone as loud as you can, Rosearians! Ya!
Cheer for everyone as loud as you can, Rosearians! Yeah!
QUEEN MOTHER - ELIZABETH'S 3D SHOWCASE!
Dear Rosarians, my beautiful Sparks of Joy,
the smiles and happiness I get from performing for y'all
I'll cherish and forever appreciate.
Thank you for making my wishes come true!
BIG HUGS my BLOODFLAME KINGDOM! - Liz